The other person is a sex friend.
相手はセフレです
Are you a sex friend?
セフレですか?
It's a sex friend.
セフレです
How many sex friends do you have?
セフレ何人いるんですか?
There is only one sex friend.
セフレは一人だけです
Only one person?
一人だけ?
Isn't that your boyfriend?
彼氏じゃないの?
It's not my boyfriend.
彼氏じゃないです
sex friend?
セフレ?
It's a sex friend.
セフレです
I feel like I said something stupid.
やばいこと言ってしまった気がします
Isn't it okay?
いいんじゃない?
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
Is it okay to hide your face with a mask?
顔をマスクで隠したりとかいい?
Is it particularly okay?
特に大丈夫か?
Well, it's kind of selfish.
ですね、なんか勝手悪いです
OK
yes.
はい
It's selfish.
勝手悪い
Is it okay to have sex on the third day?
セックス3日目でいい?
It's quite recent.
結構最近です
What do you want to do?
どんなことしたいとか?
Normal, well, it's normal today.
普通、まあ今日ノーマルっていうか普通のやつですけど
Yes, it seems normal.
はい、ノーマルみたいですね
Is normal okay?
ノーマルでいいですか?
yes.
はい
Amazing
すげ
What?
え って
is that so?
そうですか?
Yeah.
うん
It's no longer beautiful.
綺麗くなくなった
happy.
うれしい
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
Can I take pictures?
撮 れる?
Yeah.
うん
Can I have your picture taken?
撮ってもらっていい?
Yeah.
うん
I don't think so.
そうは思いませんが
Eh, is that okay?
え、いいですか?
Yeah.
うん
You're good at it.
上手じゃん
Yeah.
うん
He's good at it.
上手だ
Yeah.
うん
It's big, it's bigger.
大きいからね、もっと大きい
big?
大きい?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it usually big?
普通、やっぱり大きくない?
picture?
え?
Are you taking pills?
ピル飲んでたりする?
I'm planning to start doing it next month.
来月からやるのも予定です
Ah, okay.
あっ、オッケー
It's better to take a pill.
ピル飲んだほうがいいですよ
yeah?
ん?
It's better to take a pill.
ピル飲んだほうがいいですよ
oh dear
まあ
Hey, I'll be able to get a semen disease test and tell you my real story.
ね、 精病検査して、生の話ができちゃう
Will you come?
来るかな?
I'm taking home pay.
手取りはしてる
Make it this front.
この辺頭にして
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様でした
It felt good.
気 持ちよかった
Oh, really?
え、そう?
it was good.
良かった
I thought it didn't hurt.
痛くなかったかな、と思って
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様でした
Yes, sorry.
はい、 ごめん
yes.
はい
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかったですか?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
What, don't you want to sleep already?
え、もう寝たくならん?
Yeah.
うん
Shall I go to sleep? Don't you go to school?
寝ようか、もう学校行かない?
Like.
みたいな
It's getting a little rough now.
今、ちょっとなってますね
That's right.
だよね
yes.
はい
It's dazzling.
眩しいですね